One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
What the hell is this?
I thought we trapped the lightning one!
You've got some nerve...
to do this to me, Kid!
I'll see to it...
that you're severely punished
for dropping me into the sea!
Prepare yourself.
What should we do?
This ain't lookin' good for us.
Old hag's got some spunk.
Not only that...
she seems a helluva lot more powerful!
Crap...
We'd better...
get outta here!
There's no escape!
Time to test your abilities!
Show me what you've got,
Hera!
Okay, Mama!
Fulgora!
Extend your hand, no need to fear
Cut through the wind, and persevere
Chart your own course, the time to push forward is here
In a time like a storm, hear the tidal waves roar,
we keep trudging along but we're still wanting more
But in spite of it all, the foundation we built
for ourselves was about to fall
Where the compass points - Is it right? Is it wrong?
Who to ask? As if there's anyone listening
I guess you'll never be one hundred percent sure
But if you shut your eyes to the chaos,
and you'd only take a breath
When you open up your eyes
you will find where you were meant to be
Extend your hand, no need to fear
Cut through the wind, and persevere
Kick out the dark until the sky clears
Even as we act in our own best interests,
doing what we each believe is for our own
Chart your own course, the time to push forward is here
The Sweet Bean Code
Killer...
You there?
Yeah...
Dammit...
She really knocked us into next week.
Yeah...
Alright, so... where are we?
Guest Parlor
Inside
the Castle
Looks like we're back inside the castle...
Where's Big Mom?
She's not coming after us.
Judging by the size of that hole,
she probably lost track of
where she sent us.
Kid!
Where are you?!
I'm gonna...
slaughter you!
Well, I guess she's down there.
I'm not gonna let that old crone
team up with Kaido again!
I'm sending her to hell!
Let's hustle!
Straw Sword!
It's you...!
Hawkins!
Basil Hawkins "the Magician" of the Worst Generation
Headliner, Beast Pirates
You son of a...
You've got a lot of nerve to come attack us.
You traitor!
I was betrayed by Apoo, just like you.
I merely avoided a fight
I knew I couldn't win.
Smart move.
No wonder you haven't made it big.
If you're so weak that you know you'll lose,
don't ever show your face...
on the battlefield again!
I'm impressed you're both still alive.
Shut your trap already!
Just breathing the same air as you
makes me wanna throw up!
Kid, you go on ahead.
We can't leave Big Mom unchecked.
I'll...
take care of him.
Appreciate it.
Kid's running away! After him!
Many thanks.
I didn't stand a chance two-on-one.
Demon Face!
You're doing a great job as
a Headliner for the Beast Pirates.
You're totally domesticated.
Say whatever you like.
Your probability of
dying here is 92 percent.
How pitiful, Kamazo the Reaper.
Fortune-telling again?
We take matters into our own hands.
I wish you luck, Killer.
Screw you.
I don't want even one tiny bit...
of your damn luck.
You guys need to just...
give it up already!
The dino-dude jumped on!
Go away!
Usopp! Aim for his weak spots!
I got this!
We won't give up! We're not gonna die here!
Temple!
Chin!
Adam's apple!
You little...
Leave us alone, you lousy lizard!
Eyeball!
Nostril!
Just fall off already!
How much do we have to hit you?!
How the hell is he this tough?!
You can do it, Komachiyo!
We'll be there soon!
If we can get to the Performance Floor stage,
then the enemies that Horsella
and her friends fed the millet dumplings...
will follow my orders too!
And if they come to our side, then...
my job here is done!
If it means I can help everyone...
then I don't care what happens to me!
So get me to the stage!
Don't be silly, Tama!
Get a grip!
This fight's not over till we take back Wano!
Otama, keep your chin up!
This young lady and old man
will protect you at all costs!
Who are you calling an old man?!
I'm only nineteen!
I wanted to help everyone...
like Big Bro Luffy does.
But I'm...
I'm scared and can't take it anymore...
You little runt!
Don't push your luck!
Can't you see the girl is scared?!
I'm sorry, Tama.
I won't let you worry anymore.
Leave this to me!
Usopp!
Get ready, you lousy lizard!
Long-nosed pest!
Every little thing you do pisses me off!
Lethal Green Star!
What?!
What are you doing,
you long-nosed freak?!
Firework Flowers!
Hot!
Careful with that, Usopp!
Sorry!
I don't have many close-range weapons!
But I'm gonna finish him off!
Lethal Green Star!
Exploding Pine Cones!
Seriously, Usopp?!
Boom!
Direct hit!
You like that, you freak?!
Lizard extermination complete!
You pest...
You pest!
He's back up!
The dino fruit guys are insane!
Dammit...
That long-nosed pain-in-the-neck!
If only a millet dumpling worked on him...!
It only works on smile fruit eaters!
What should we do if he comes back?!
Get out here, Kid!
– What?!
– Big Mom?!
On the Roof
Huh? I'm free...
Where's Mama?
Mama! Where are you?!
I'll be right there, Mama!
Mama, where are you?!
Say something! I'll be helpful!
Looks like Eustass got weaker.
Big Mom is back inside the castle...
It won't be good if she
comes back for that thundercloud.
Hey!
I'm taking everyone but you!
Got it!
Mama!
Seems like you're having fun.
The worse things get, the more you smile.
And the bigger your smile...
Luffy!
Please! Defeat him!
Kaido!
Connecting Hallway
From Treasury 2F to Castle 3F
Kiku, does your arm hurt?
You needn't ask that of a samurai.
Until my life is extinguished,
it's merely an itch.
Just the way my heart itched
on the day you disappeared.
Big Brother!
Hey...
If you can still tease me,
you must be well enough.
My deepest apologies
for leaving without a word.
Izo.
If Wano is opened successfully,
how do you think it may change?
Well...
If we survive, let us
talk of this tomorrow morning.
A rather tall task!
This is all-out war! Either we win, or we die!
Their forces are surely spread thin.
I can protect Lord Momonosuke on my own!
Kanjuro is after Lord Momonosuke's life!
I will attempt to reach
Lord Momonosuke before he does,
and vanquish him myself!
The rest of you, help everyone you can!
Understood.
Okay, Kin'emon.
Cat, let us spread out!
You got it!
Best of luck!
Sir Kin!
Please allow me to vanquish Kanjuro!
I won't fail this time!
Kiku!
Follow me!
Okay!
That's...!
Master Nekomamushi!
I knew it was you!
Shishilian! Bariete!
Captain of Inuarashi's Musketeers
Mink Recon Squad
Bariete
Shishilian
Where are you dashing off to?!
We require your assistance!
You see, Pedro is...
Pedro...
is dead?!
Yes. He died in Big Mom's territory.
Were it not for him, I doubt
Luffy's crew would be here now!
I see.
Pedro...
Mew've done well.
And the man responsible
for his death is on this island?!
Yes, and we need your help!
It would seem Wanda and Carrot
are currently doing battle with him!
I was always gonna help you!
Master!
That cat is flying!
Crawl Space
First Floor
Inside the Castle
Momonosuke.
Shinobu.
Watch out for the Marys!
They're roaming around
Onigashima to do recon!
What? Where?! Where are they?!
Worry not! We have this!
It's you!
I thought so!
I'll use this to make myself a decoy!
You and I are being targeted as a pair.
So I'm gonna carry this and run for it!
Let's do this!
It is clear that you simply wish to fight.
Go ahead, Yamato.
We're in contact with Sir Kin!
I shall stay here and protect
Lord Momonosuke!
Mm-hm. I appreciate it, Shinobu!
Oh, right!
Momonosuke,
you can hear Luffy's voice, right?
Is he okay?
Mm-hm, I can hear it.
It is the same as before.
He is weaker, but still well.
But...
there are now only two voices!
A duel...
Luffy and Kaido
must be fighting head-to-head!
I need to hurry!
Oden's Travel Record
I see...
Everything regarding my father's adventures...
I had heard so many stories about him...
but to see them written out like this...
Why...?!
It's you two!
The Cat Burglar and the long-nosed one...
– She's gonna kill us!
You're Straw Hat's crewmates.
Olin!
Otama!
Hello there, Otama!
What in the world are you doing
in such a dangerous place?
I've been worried about you, Olin!
You suddenly disappeared in Udon!
I'm sorry.
But I've worried so much about you, too!
I'm not mad! I'm happy to see you again!
Great! Thank you so much for
taking care of me when I lost my memory!
Oh, good! You got it back!
Mm-hm!
Crap...
Mama's gone into mother mode!
That only happens around kids ten and under!
H-H-Hold on, Otama!
I-Is she your friend?!
You look so pretty in a kimono!
You really think so?!
I got a new hairpin!
Otama! Get her out of here!
Hey, the person who did my hair...
You know, that poor busybody
from Okobore Town...
Oh, Otsuru!
How is she doing?
I may have only had a little,
but I'll never forget the taste of that oshiruko!
It was so delicious!
I wish I could eat it again.
Actually, Olin...
Okobore Town...
is gone now.
Gone? What do you mean, "gone"?
The samurai are the ones who ate
all the food before the raid,
but it ended up getting
pinned on the townsfolk.
And then Kaido's followers...
burned the town to the ground!
What?
Olin.
So good!
It's yummy!
They're rebels!
Don't let 'em get away!
Light 'em up! And their houses, too!
The people of Okobore Town were...
Otsuru!
My, you look simply stunning, Olin!
You think so?
You look super cute!
Kaido's subservient freaks...!
Destroy this town and its people!
Burn it to the ground!
The people who helped me
when I lost my memory...
Olin!
Everyone...
Everyone in Okobore Town
who treated me with such kindness...
You're telling me they destroyed it?!
The dino-dude is coming!
Go away! We're busy with something!
Book it, Komachiyo!
Hey, Big Mom!
Don't let them past you!
Go, Komachiyo!
Too late! It's over for you!
You bunch of brutes...
Even in the cruel world of pirates,
there's still a code of honor!
Damn you!
You clowns!
Over there?! Big Mom!
It's Mama!
I'm so glad she's alive!
Are you okay, Komachiyo?!
Hang in there!